class Database {
  static List<Map> qa = [
    {
      "question":
          "What programing language is primarily used in flutter developement ?",
      "options": ["Java", "Swift", "Dart", "Python"],
      "answer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which widget in flutter is used to create a button with a touchable area ?",
      "options": ["Text", "Button", "GestureDetector", "InkWell"],
      "answer": 4,
    },
    {
      "question": "Which file is used to define the apps's routes in flutter ?",
      "options": [
        "main.dart",
        "apps_routes.dart",
        "routes.dart",
        "route_config.dart"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question": "Flutter is developed and maintained by which company ?",
      "options": ["Google", "Apple", "Facebook", "Microsoft"],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What command is used to create a new Flutter project from the command line ?",
      "options": [
        "flutter start",
        "flutter init",
        "flutter create",
        "flutter new"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which Flutter widget is used to create a scrollable list of widgets ?",
      "options": ["Text", "Column", "ListView", "Stack"],
      "answer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What is the primary purpose of the 'pubspec.yaml' file in a Flutter project ?",
      "options": [
        "Storing app data",
        "Defining the app's layout",
        "Managing project dependencies",
        "Setting app permissions"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which of the following is not a state management technique in Flutter ?",
      "options": ["Provider", "Redux", "HTTP", "BLoC"],
      "answer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Flutter allows you to develop apps for which of the following platforms ?",
      "options": [
        "Android and iOS",
        "Windows and macOS",
        "Web",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": 4,
    },
    {
      "question": "In Flutter, what does the term " 'widget' " refer to ?",
      "options": [
        "A small app",
        "A user interface element",
        "A JavaScript library",
        "A Flutter developer"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
    },
  ];
}
